any chance you'd let me peek under the
hood of your make me I loved reading
your journal I'm so jealous you get to
go to all those places that's true I
guess you don't get to travel very much
a giant gorilla just like in those old
video game I get that a lot
this is no place for children
oh are you calling a child war isn't a
game
are you sure life isn't a game soldier
76 hmm youth truly is wasted on the
young
oh come on I bet you got up to all sorts
of trouble when you were my age diva
just tell me one thing
where'd you learn to shoot like that
16-bit hero diva have you seen the
swatter course no that is what I call a
Mac sighs isn't everything
jenji I heard you used to have all the
high scores here that's right wait used
to hey where did they all go
oh I can't stand you hackers you give
those of us with still a bad name you
know that isn't the kind of hacking I do
right seeing what happened after the war
here gives me hope for the rebuilding of
my country things can be destroyed but
as long as the people are strong they
can always be rebuilt
Divac in the flesh Oh can I get your
autograph only if I could get yours too
I love your new album
hey I was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
of course here you go love diva Oh after
this match is over right now it's time
to get serious